// // var questions12 = [{
// // 		"question":"1. What’s the main point of difference between human & machine intelligence?",
// // 		"option1":"human perceive everything as pattern when machine perceive merely as data",
// // 		"option2":"human have emotions",
// // 		"option3":" human have sense organs",
// // 		"option4":"human have abilities of a robot",
// // 		"correctanswer":"1"
// // }, {
// // "question":"Among the following which is not a horn clause",
// // "option1":"p",
// // "option2":"Øp V q",
// // "option3":"p → q",
// // "option4":"p → Øq",
// // "correctanswer":"4"
// // }, {
// // "question":"In LISP, the function returns t if is a CONS cell and nil otherwise:",
// // "option1":"(cons <object>)",
// // "option2":"(consp <object>)",
// // "option3":"(eq <object>)",
// // "option4":"(cous = <object>)",
// // "correctanswer":"2"
// // }, {
// // "question":"what do you mean by proponent?",
// // "option1":"Propound a idea",
// // "option2":"Settling up opponent",
// // "option3":"Catergorizing data",
// // "option4":"Judging an person's behaviour",
// // "correctanswer":"1"
// // }, {
// //
// // }];
// var questions = [{
// 	"question": "What’s the main point of difference between human & machine intelligence?",
// 	"option1": "human perceive everything as pattern when machine perceive merely as data",
// 	"option2": "human have emotions",
// 	"option3": "human have sense organs",
// 	"option4": " human have abilities of a robot",
// 	"answer": "2"
// }, {
// 	"question":"Among the following which is not a horn clause",
// "option1":"p",
// "option2":"Øp V q",
// "option3":"p → q",
// "option4":"p → Øq",
// "answer":"4"
// }, {
// 	"question":"In LISP, the function returns t if is a CONS cell and nil otherwise:",
// "option1":"(cons <object>)",
// "option2":"(consp <object>)",
// "option3":"(eq <object>)",
// "option4":"(cous = <object>)",
// "answer":"2"
// }, {
// 	"question": "C is ?",
// 	"option1": "A third generation high level language",
// 	"option2": "A machine language",
// 	"option3": "An assembly language",
// 	"option4": "All of the above",
// 	"answer": "1"
// }, {
// 	"question":"What do you mean by vie?",
// "option1":"Complete",
// "option2":"compete",
// "option3":"Counter",
// "option4":"All the above",
// "answer":"2"
// }];
var questions = [{
	"question": "What's the main point of difference between human & machine intelligence?",
	"option1": "human perceive everything as pattern when machine perceive merely as data",
	"option2": "human have emotions",
	"option3": "human have sense organs",
	"option4": "human have abilities of a robot",
	"corr": "You are absolutely correct",
	"worr":"You are absolutely wrong",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "what do you mean by proponent?",
	"option1": "Propound a idea",
	"option2": "Settling up opponent",
	"option3": "Catergorizing data",
	"option4": "Judging an person's behaviour",
	"corr": "You are absolutely correct",
	"worr":"You are absolutely wrong",
	"answer": "1"
}, {
	"question": "What do you mean by vie?",
	"option1": "Complete",
	"option2": "compete",
	"option3": "Counter",
	"option4": "All the above",
	"answer": "2"
}, {
	"question": "Among the following which is not a horn clause",
	"option1": "p",
	"option2": "Øp V q",
	"option3": "p → q",
	"option4": "p → Øq",
	"answer": "4"
}, {
	"question": "In LISP, the function returns t if is a CONS cell and nil otherwise:",
	"option1": "cons <object>",
	"option2": "consp <object>",
	"option3": "eq <object>",
	"option4": "cons = <object>",
	"answer": "2"
}];
